<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Recipe xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema"
Name="AlertTemplate"
xmlns="http://schemas.microsoft.com/pag/gax-core"
Bound="false">
    <DocumentationLinks>
        <Link Url="http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/ms452873.aspx" Caption="MS SharePoint Developer Documentation Team Blog: Customizing Alert Notifications and Alert Templates in Windows SharePoint Services 3.0" Kind="Documentation"/>
        <Link Url="http://blogs.msdn.com/sharepointdeveloperdocs/archive/2007/12/14/how-to-customizing-alert-emails-using-ialertnotificationhandler.aspx" Caption="MS SharePoint Developer Documentation Team Blog: How To: Customizing alert emails using IAlertNotifyHandler"  Kind="Documentation"/>
    </DocumentationLinks>
    <xi:include href="../../../TypeAlias.xml" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />
    <Caption>Alert Template</Caption>
  <Description>Adds an alert template which can be used to send customized alerts.</Description>
  <HostData>
    <Icon File="Help/Icons/icon_Advanced.ico" />
    <CommandBar Menu="SPSFSolutionAdvanced"/>
    <CommandBar Menu="SPSFProjectAdvanced"/>
    <spsf:MetaData
      Visible="false"
      BindingType="CustomizationReference"
      BindingTypeTemplate="CustomizationReferenceTemplate"
      Enabled="false"
      CreateVSTemplate="true"
	  NotSandboxSupported="true"
      Category="Advanced" xmlns:spsf="http://spsf.codeplex.com">
      <spsf:Authors>
        <spsf:Author>Torsten Mandelkow</spsf:Author>
        <spsf:Author>Matthias Einig</spsf:Author>
      </spsf:Authors>
      <spsf:VersionHistory>
          <spsf:VersionHistoryEntry>1.1 Updated Documentation</spsf:VersionHistoryEntry>
          <spsf:VersionHistoryEntry>1.0 Initial Recipe</spsf:VersionHistoryEntry>
      </spsf:VersionHistory>
      <spsf:WebPageContent>
        <![CDATA[Alerts are an e-mail subscription notification service in Windows SharePoint Services 3.0. Users can create alerts to be notified of changes to list items (item level alert), documents, lists (list level alert), or document libraries. Alerts in Windows SharePoint Services 3.0 are quite flexible; when you create an alert you have options such as when to be notified and what kind of changes will trigger the alert. Alerts can be managed by users and administrators and customized by developers.

After an alert has been created, changes that fit the criteria specified in the alert are recorded in an event log. Alerts are generated by a timer job that reads the event log, formats the alert email using an alert template, and then sends that email out to the user.

Alert templates are stored in Alerttemplates.xml. Alerttemplates.xml defines the format, contents, and properties used to create alert messages from each list type in Windows SharePoint Services 3.0. Developers can customize alerts by modifying a copy of Alerttemplates.xml and then loading the customized alert templates using the stsadm -o updatealerttemplates command.
(Source: Microsoft SharePoint Developer Documentation Team Blog)

This recipe creates such an alert template.
]]>
      </spsf:WebPageContent>
    </spsf:MetaData>
  </HostData>
</Recipe>